A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3 FA456
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3
undated
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller).
FA456
10.8 Cubic Feet 9 record storage cartons.
Other Finding Aids
For other Nelson A. Rockefeller photographic holdings, please see the following finding aids:
FA454 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Nelson A. Rockefeller family, Series 1008
FA455 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Room 5600, Rockefeller family office, Series 2
FA457 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 4
FA458 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, Robert A. (Bob) Wands, Series 5
FA459 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6
FA460 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Unprocessed photographs, Series 7
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Photographic negatives cannot be handled or viewed by researchers due to the fragile nature of the format. To request duplication of an image(s), please contact an Archivist.
File Plan note
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records are formerly classified as III 15.
Notations to RG 15 are used in this collection guide. If/when the notations in this guide are revised, an updated version of the guide will be made available for scholarly access.
Arrangement note
The Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs are arranged in the following series:
Series 1008: Nelson A. Rockefeller family. Series 2: Room 5600, Rockefeller family office. Series 3: Gubernatorial Press Office. Series 4: Gubernatorial Press Office. Series 5: Gubernatorial, Robert A. (Bob) Wands. Series 6: Vice Presidential. Series 7: Unprocessed photographs.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for scholarly research. Requests for material are to be made by Box Number.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Arrangement note
Rockefeller family photographic holdings are arranged into the following series:
Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001. William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002. John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003. William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004. John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005. Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006. John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007. Nelson A. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1008. Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009. David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010.
Other Finding Aids note
For other Rockefeller family photographic holdings, please see the following finding aids:
FA445 Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001
FA446 William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002
FA447 John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003
FA448 William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004
FA449 John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005
FA450 Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006
FA451 John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007
FA452 Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009
FA453 David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010
Art, Modern; New York (N.Y.); Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Arts; State governments -- United States; Rockefeller family -- Art collections; Political campaigns -- United States; New York (State); Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich); New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller).
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 3; 10.8 Cubic Feet 9 record storage cartons.
  General note
  KEY
  1008
  Nelson A. Rockefeller
  .15
  Record Group number; 15, Gubernatorial
  /123
  Image identification number; used for loose, miscellaneous photographs
  /Roll819A
  Photographer's roll number; utilizes a photographer's numbering system for a large series of photographs, usually used to identify contact sheets (a contact sheet bears several separate images on a single piece of photographic paper showing all, or a portion, of the images on a roll of film)
  Numbers in ( )
  Number of images on a contact sheet
  EXAMPLES
  1008.15/123
  Image number (not from a contact sheet)
  (18), 1008.15/Roll819A
  Identification number for a contact sheet bearing 18 images
  1008.15/Roll819A/12
  Identifying number for a distinct image on a contact sheet, in this case frame number 12
  - San Diego, Nelson A. Rockefeller at rally, 1956 September 21; 1008.15/345 (Box 1)
  - Beth Israel Hospital, Cornerstone, Nelson A. Rockefeller, others, 1958; 1008.15/566 - 1008.15/567 (Box 1)
  - Binghamton, NY, Fair, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Anne Marie, Steven, 1958; 1008.15/409 - 1008.15/418 (Box 1)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1958; 1008.15/6 (Box 1)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, unidentified man, 1958; 1008.15/522 - 1008.15/523 (Box 1)
  - New York, General Herkimer Hotel, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, circa 1958; 1008.15/561 (Box 1)
  - Photographs by Captain Tom Abello, circa 1958; 1008.15/537 - 1008.15/539 (Box 1)
  - Hotel Pontiac, Oswego, NY, 1958 October; 1008.15/562 (Box 1)
  - Columbian Republican League Reception, Fred Pitteria, 1958 October 28; 1008.15/558 - 1008.15/560 (Box 1)
  - Albany, Red Room, Roy Kennedy as Samuel de Champlain, Grant Johnson, 1959; 1008.15/494 (Box 1)
  - Alfred E. Smith Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Cardinal, John F. Kennedy, 1959; 1008.15/285 - 1008.15/289 (Box 1)
  - American Jewish Committee, Anti Defamation League Dinner, Label Katz, 1959; 1008.15/322 (Box 1)
    - Andrew Goodman, Jacob M. Kaplan, Jerome Newman, Jacob Blaustein, 1008.15/323
    - Henry E. Schultz, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1008.15/324
    - Herbert Ehrmann, president of American Jewish Committee, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1008.15/325
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Jacob Blaustein, 1008.15/326 - 1008.15/327
  - Copenhagen, airport photos, day of wedding of Steven and Anne Marie, 1959; 1008.15/292 - 1008.15/295 (Box 1)
  - County Officers Association, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959; 1008.15/321 (Box 1)
  - D141, Federation of Jewish Philanthropies, The Heating Machine, 1959; 1008.15/2738 (Box 1)
  - Governor's Mansion, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, others, 1959; 1008.15/250 - 1008.15/265 (Box 1)
  - HRH Beatrix dancing with Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959; 1008.15/348 (Box 1)
  - Minneapolis, Nelson A. Rockefeller receives "honorary citizen," Mayor P. Kenneth Peterson, 1959; 1008.15/267 - 1008.15/268 (Box 1)
  - D214, Nelson A. Rockefeller, three men, 1959; 1008.15/2559 (Box 1)
  - NY Mirror Photographs, 1959; 1008.15/526 - 1008.15/534 (Box 1)
  - D143, NY City, Biltmore, Community Service Social Rally, 1959; 1008.15/2741 (Box 1)
  - NY City, Hudson Celebration, Nelson A. Rockefeller at podium, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959; 1008.15/454 - 1008.15/459 (Box 1)
  - NYS. Fair, Nelson A. Rockefeller with contestants, 1959; 1008.15/84- 1008.15/85 (Box 1)
  - NYU. Medical Center, Nelson A. Rockefeller at podium, 1959; 1008.15/315 (Box 1)
  - Rochester, NY, Nelson A. Rockefeller shaking Officer Nicholas Digiro's hand, 1959; 1008.15/347 (Box 1)
  - Albany, Red Room, Nelson A. Rockefeller shakes woman's hand, circa 1959; 1008.15/564 (Box 1)
  - Face the Nation, circa 1959; 1008.15/280 - 1008.15/284 (Box 1)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, cap and gown, unidentified men, circa 1959; 1008.15/275 (Box 1)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Congressman T.M. Pelly, circa 1959; 1008.15/453 (Box 1)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller dinner function, circa 1959; 1008.15/569- 1008.15/570 (Box 1)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller speaking at podium, circa 1959; 1008.15/1 (Box 1)
  - NYS. Women's Legislative Forum, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller in audience, circa 1959; 1008.15/563 (Box 1)
  - Red Room. Farm Bureau meeting, 1959 February; 1008.15/344 (Box 1)
  - Capitol Lobby, "Half Moon," Hudson Champlain Celebration, 1959 February 2; 1008.15/565 (Box 1)
  - Red Room. Remington Rand Division Sperry Rand Corporation, 1959 March 3; 1008.15/535 (Box 1)
    - Charles Gosnell, Walter Van Wiggeren, H.J. Syren, 1008.15/536
  - "Scripture Reading at the Inauguration" of Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 March 9; 1008.15/568 (Box 1)
  - Inaugural Dinner of the United Jewish Appeal, 1959 March 12; 1008.15/540 - 1008.15/545 (Box 1)
  - Young Adult Council of the National Social Welfare Assembly, 1959 April 14; 1008.15/524 (Box 1)
    - Dr. Parikh, Mrs. Shah, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mr. Ramkrishna Bajaj, Mrs. Bajaj, 1008.15/525
  - NY City Coliseum, Boy Scouts of America Exhibition, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 April 17; 1008.15/495 (Box 1)
  - Buffalo, 1959 May; 1008.15/509 - 1008.15/520 (Box 1)
  - State University Teachers College at Plattsburgh, Dedication Program, 1959 May 5; 1008.15/496 - 1008.15/508 (Box 1)
  - University of Houston, TX, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Louis and Sonia Silverman, 1959 May 28; 1008.15/232 (Box 1)
  - NYS., Civil Defense Warning System, 1959 June 17; 1008.15/483 (Box 1)
    - Maj. Gen. Condon, Kenneth Downs, William McGrath, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1008.15/484
    - General Anthony McAuliffe, Lt. General Huebner, 1008.15/485 - 1008.15/486
  - Saint Lawrence Seaway Opening, Pat Nixon, Richard Nixon, Mary Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Queen Elizabeth, 1959 June 27; 1008.15/462 - 1008.15/482 (Box 1)
  - Opening of St Lawrence Seaway, 1959 June 27; 1008.15/488 - 1008.15/493 (Box 1)
  - Seaway Dedication Ceremonies, Richard Nixon, Queen Elizabeth, 1959 June 27; 1008.15/343 (Box 1)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller and boy scouts, 1959 July; 1008.15/487 (Box 1)
  - D103, 55th Street, Westchester Magazine, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, 1959 July 2; 1008.15/2304 (Box 1)
  - Automobile Club of New York, Nelson A. Rockefeller, children and safety posters, 1959 July 9; 1008.15/449 - 1008.15/452 (Box 1)
  - D104, Coliseum, NY City, NAACP meeting, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 July 13; 1008.15/2305 - 1008.15/2308 (Box 1)
  - Camp Drum, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Brig. General Stevenson, Lt. Colonel Albert Acciardi, Private Michael O'Hara, 1959 July 18; 1008.15/521 (Box 1)
  - 42nd Division Parade at Wheeler Sack Field, Nelson A. Rockefeller, General Nast, General Stevenson, General Cox, General Stuart, 1959 July 18; 1008.15/328 - 1008.15/342 (Box 1)
    - National Guardsman Magazine, NY Edition, 1959 September
  - Camp Drum, Nelson A. Rockefeller, photo by Captain Tom Abello, 1959 July 18; 1008.15/291 (Box 1)
  - "Meet the Press," Marquis Childs, Clinton Daniel, James Desmond, Lawrence Spivak, Governor Munoz Marin, 1959 July 21; 1008.15/460 - 1008.15/461 (Box 1)
  - Fort Ticonderoga, 1959 July 26; 1008.15/350- 1008.15/360 (Box 1)
  - Fort Ticongeroga, "Champlain Day," Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 July 26; 1008.15/290 (Box 1)
  - D105, Monticello, NY, 10-Mile River Boy Scout Camp, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 July 28; 1008.15/2309- 1008.15/2314 (Box 1)
  - Puerto Rico, Governors' Conference, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 August; 1008.15/296 - 1008.15/320 (Box 1)
  - D106, Barbizon Plaza, National Association of Budget Officers, 1959 August 19; 1008.15/2315 (Box 1)
  - D108, Idlewild Airport, Nelson A. Rockefeller and daughters, 1959 August 20; 1008.15/2329 (Box 1)
  - D107, Jones Beach, 30th Anniversary of Jones Beach State Park, 1959 August 20; 1008.15/2316- 1008.15/2328 (Box 1)
  - Jones Beach, NY, 35th Anniversary, Robert Moses, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 August 20; 1008.15/599 - 1008.15/617 (Box 1)
  - D109, Idlewild Airport, Steven, Anne Marie, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 August 24; 1008.15/2330 - 1008.15/2337 (Box 1)
  - D111, 55th Street, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Eleanor Harris, 1959 August 26; 1008.15/2338 (Box 1)
  - D112, Albany, NY, Miss New York State Fair, 1959 August 27; 1008.15/2677 (Box 1)
  - D116, 55th Street, Small J.D. Meeting, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 September 3; 1008.15/2679 (Box 1)
  - D117, 55th Street, NAACP Life Membership Award, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 September 3; 1008.15/2680 - 1008.15/2681 (Box 1)
  - D118, Labor Day Parade, ILGWU members, Louis Lefkowitz, 1959 September 7; 1008.15/2682 - 1008.15/2685 (Box 1)
  - D121, Syracuse, New York State Fair, 1959 September 10; 1008.15/2686- 1008.15/2714 (Box 1)
  - D122, NY, Aquaduct Opening, Nelson A. Rockefeller cuts ribbon, 1959 September 14; 1008.15/2715 - 1008.15/2716 (Box 1)
  - D123, Primitive Museum, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Princess Beatrice, 1959 September 15; 1008.15/2717 - 1008.15/2724 (Box 1)
  - D124, 79th Street, Temple Shaaray Tefila, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 September 20; 1008.15/2725 - 1008.15/2726 (Box 1)
  - D126, 55th Street, Limited Profit Houseing Corporation, 1959 September 21; 1008.15/2727 - 1008.15/2728 (Box 1)
  - D127, Waldorf, Circus - Saints & Sinners, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 September 22; 1008.15/2729 - 1008.15/2733 (Box 1)
  - D130, 55th Street, Frank di Votto, Malcolm Wilson, 1959 September 22; 1008.15/2734 - 1008.15/2735 (Box 1)
  - D133, Garden City, Distinguished Service Award, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 September 24; 1008.15/2736 (Box 1)
  - Whitespace Inn, 1959 September 25; 1008.15/196 (Box 1)
  - D139, Commodore, NY City, Magazine Publishers Association, 1959 September 29; 1008.15/2737 (Box 1)
  - D142, 55th Street, Swearing In Commissioner Isaacson, 1959 September 30; 1008.15/2739 - 1008.15/2740 (Box 1)
  - New York Times Youth Forum, Fred Toettcher, Marie Frein, Dorothy Gordon, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Michele Bedesem, Philip Lopate, 1959 October; 1008.15/346 (Box 2)
  - D165, Syracuse, New York State Education Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 October; 1008.15/2353 - 1008.15/2357 (Box 2)
  - D144, Pharsalia, NY, State Youth Camp, 1959 October 2; 1008.15/2742 (Box 2)
  - D145, 41 Street & 5th Avenue, Pulaski Day Parade, 1959 October 4; 1008.15/2743 - 1008.15/2747 (Box 2)
  - D146, Starlight Roof, Waldorf, Pulaski Day Dinner, 1959 October 4; 1008.15/2748 - 1008.15/2754 (Box 2)
  - D151, 55th Street, Civil Rights Bureau, 1959 October 9; 1008.15/2755 - 1008.15/2756 (Box 2)
  - D152, NY City, Employ the Handicapped Luncheon, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 October 9; 1008.15/2757 (Box 2)
  - Columbus Day dinner, Paul Cassavina, Robert Wagner, Fortune Pope, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Manlio Brosio, 1959 October 12; 1008.15/349 (Box 2)
  - D154, 62 Street & 5th Avenue, Columbus Day Parade, 1959 October 12; 1008.15/2758 - 1008.15/2773 (Box 2)
  - D155, Astor, NY City, Eastern Star, 1959 October 14; 1008.15/2774 - 1008.15/2775 (Box 1)
  - D159, Waldorf, NY City, YWCA Luncheon, 1959 October 21; 1008.15/2776 - 1008.15/2778 (Box 1)
  - D160, Waldorf, NY City, Al Smith Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 October 22; 1008.15/2779 - 1008.15/2783 (Box 1)
  - D162, Auburn, NY, Luncheon, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Maurice I. Schwartz, 1959 October 26; 1008.15/2342 - 1008.15/2345, and 1008.15/2560 (Box 1)
  - D163, Syracuse, NY, Bristol Meyers Dedication, 1959 October 26; 1008.15/2346 - 1008.15/2352, and 1008.15/2564 (Box 1)
  - D167, 40th Street, NY Republican Head Quarters, Bernard Newman Judicial Candidates, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Louis Lefkowitz, 1959 October 28; 1008.15/2358 - 1008.15/2359 (Box 1)
  - D168, NY City, President Sedou Toure of Guinea, Primitive Museum, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 November 4; 1008.15/2360 - 1008.15/2361 (Box 1)
  - D169, 55th Street, Gail-Whit Mauzy of Windham, NY, 1959 November 4; 1008.15/2362 - 1008.15/2363 (Box 1)
  - D170, NY City, Federation of Protestant Welfare Luncheon, 1959 November 5; 1008.15/2364 - 1008.15/2375 (Box 1)
  - D171, St. Regis, NY City, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 November 5; 1008.15/2376 - 1008.15/2377 (Box 1)
  - D172, Waldorf, NY City, Economic Club Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 November 9; 1008.15/2378 - 1008.15/2379 (Box 1)
  - Press and Union League Club, Fred Southerland, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Bob Alderman, 1959 November 13; 1008.15/276 - 1008.15/278 (Box 1)
  - D174, 4 Seasons & Modern Museum, 30th Anniversary Fund Raising Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, 1959 November 16; 1008.15/2380 - 1008.15/2382 (Box 2)
  - D175, Roosevelt, NY City, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Eleanor Roosevelt, 1959 November 16; 1008.15/2383 - 1008.15/2385 (Box 2)
  - D176, Waldorf, NY City, World Trade Dinner, National Foreign Trade Convention, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 November 16; 1008.15/2386 - 1008.15/2389 (Box 2)
  - D180, 55th Street, Governor Underwood of West Virginia, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 November 18; 1008.15/2414 - 1008.15/2415 (Box 2)
  - D177, 55th Street, New York American Legion, Nelson A. Rockefeller, National Commander Martin B. McKneally, 1959 November 19; 1008.15/2390 - 1008.15/2399 (Box 2)
  - D178, 52 Street, Woman's National Repubican Club, 1959 November 19; 1008.15/2400 - 1008.15/2405 (Box 2)
  - Commodore, NY City, Testimonial dinner, Martin B. McKneally, 1959 November 19; 1008.15/266 - 1008.15/274 (Box 2)
  - D179, Commodore, American Legion Dinner, 1959 November 19; 1008.15/2406 - 1008.15/2413 (Box 2)
  - D181, Convaire Airport, Plane Trip to Providence, RI, from Marine Terminal, 1959 November 20; 1008.15/2416 - 1008.15/2425 (Box 2)
  - D182, Sheraton-Biltmore, Providence, RI, Press Conference and TV Panel Show, 1959 November 20; 1008.15/2426 - 1008.15/2428 (Box 2)
  - D183, Providence, RI Republican Committee Luncheon, 1959 November 20; 1008.15/2429 (Box 2)
  - D184, Providence, RI, WPRO taped TV show, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 November 20; 1008.15/2430 - 1008.15/2435 (Box 2)
  - D185, Providence, Society of Newspaper Editors Dinner, 1959 November 20; 1008.15/2436 - 1008.15/2443, and 1008.15/2563 - 1008.15/2569 (Box 2)
  - D186, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, others, 1959 November 30; 1008.15/2444 - 1008.15/2446 (Box 2)
  - D187, Albany, Conference Room, Staff Meeting, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 November 30; 1008.15/2447 - 1008.15/2452 (Box 2)
  - Providence, RI, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Michael Ogden, 1959 November 30; 1008.15/279 (Box 2)
  - D188-A, Biltmore, Little White House Conference for Aging Luncheon, 1959 December 1; 1008.15/2453 (Box 2)
  - D189, Roosevelt, NY City, Civil Defense Meeting Luncheon, Bomb shelter, Nelson A. Rockefeller, children, 1959 December 4; 1008.15/2454 (Box 2)
  - D190, 55th Street, Swearing In Joseph Gimma, Harness Racing Commission, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, 1959 December 4; 1008.15/2455 - 1008.15/2458 (Box 2)
  - D191, 55th Street, Junior Chamber of Commerce, Robert Clark, Lewis Aronowitz, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 December 4; 1008.15/2459 (Box 2)
  - D192, 55th Street, Publisher Armed Services Committee, Lutheran Church, 1959 December 4; 1008.15/2460 - 1008.15/2466 (Box 2)
  - D193, 55th Street, Morning side Community Center, Lewis Robinson, Ellington, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 December 4; 1008.15/2467 - 1008.15/2470 (Box 2)
  - D194, Waldorf, NY City, New York Bible Society Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 December 4; 1008.15/2471 - 1008.15/2472 (Box 2)
  - D195, Governor's Mansion, Reception for Legislative Leaders, 1959 December 7; 1008.15/2473 - 1008.15/2478 (Box 2)
  - D196, Convair 404, Airplane trip from Albany to Newark, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 December 8; 1008.15/2479 - 1008.15/2481 (Box 2)
  - D197, Astor, NY City, Jane Todd Testimonial Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 December 9; 1008.15/2482 - 1008.15/2485 (Box 2)
  - D198, South Bend, IN, Seven State Trip, Nelson A. Rockefeller, nuns, 1959 December 12; 1008.15/2486 - 1008.15/2494 (Box 2)
  - D199, St. Louis, MO, Airplane, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1959 December 13; 1008.15/2495 - 1008.15/2497 (Box 2)
  - D200, Minneapolis Jr. Chamber of Commerce, 1959 December 14; 1008.15/2498 - 1008.15/2510 (Box 2)
  - D201, Seven State Trip, St. Paul, MN, 1959 December 14; 1008.15/2511 - 1008.15/2520 (Box 2)
  - D202, Seven State Trip, Madison, WI, 1959 December 15; 1008.15/2521 - 1008.15/2526 (Box 2)
  - D203, Seven State Trip, Milwaukee, Nelson A. Rockefeller at a convention, 1959 December 15; 1008.15/2527 - 1008.15/2533 (Box 2)
  - D204, Seven State Trip, Green Bay, WI, 1959 December 16; 1008.15/2534 - 1008.15/2536 (Box 2)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Visits Racine, Wise and Johnson's Wax, 1959 December 16; 1008.15/173 - 1008.15/188 (Box 2)
  - D205, Seven State Trip, Houston, TX, 1959 December 17; 1008.15/2537 - 1008.15/2543 (Box 2)
  - D206, Seven State Trip, Dallas, TX, 1959 December 17; 1008.15/2544 - 1008.15/2552 (Box 2)
  - D207, Seven State Trip, Houston, TX, 1959 December 17; 1008.15/2553 - 1008.15/2554 (Box 2)
  - D208, Seven State Trip, Miami, FL, 1959 December 18; 1008.15/2555 - 1008.15/2556 (Box 2)
  - D209, Plane Trip from Miami, Guy Savino, Hugh Morrow, 1959 December 24; 1008.15/2557 - 1008.15/2558 (Box 2)
  - California, Governor Pat Brown of California, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960; 1008.15/71 (Box 3)
    - Dr. Carryon, L.A. Master of Ceremonies or Fiesta, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1008.15/72 - 1008.15/78
  - California, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Hannah Nixon, John Rousselot, 1960; 1008.15/92 - 1008.15/94 (Box 3)
  - California, Photos by Burton's Studio, Hannah Nixon, John Rousselot, 1960; 1008.15/98 - 1008.15/108 (Box 3)
  - California, Berkley, 1960; 1008.15/4 - 1008.15/5 (Box 3)
  - Germany, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Chancellor Adinam, Greg Fedon of Consol. Guard, 1960; 1008.15/234 - 1008.15/235 (Box 3)
  - Grossingers, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960; 1008.15/129 - 1008.15/131 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960; 1008.15/1321 (Box 3)
  - Florence Hanah, John Gorrah, Grant Sawyer, Bette Sawyer, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960; 1008.15/1322 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, boarding airplane, 1960; 1008.15/86 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, photograph by Constructioneer of NY, 1960; 1008.15/231 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, photograph by Donald E. Dobbs, 1960; 1008.15/1289 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, photographs by Jack Schildkraut, 1960; 1008.15/142 - 1008.15/144 (Box 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller visits Richard Nixon in the Hospital, 1960; 1008.15/132 - 1008.15/141 (Box 3)
  - IL, Chicago, Republican National Convention, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960; 1008.15/90 - 1008.15/91 (Box 3)
  - IN, Notre Dame, 1960; 1008.15/1319 - 1008.15/1320 (Box 3)
  - MA, Taunton, Roseland Ballroom, Testimonial for Joe Martin, Ginnie Hillman, 1960; 1008.15/89 (Box 3)
  - Minnesota, Elmer L. Anderson, 1960; 1008.15/1290 (Box 3)
  - NJ, Nixon Rally, 1960; 1008.15/109 - 1008.15/122 (Box 3)
  - NJ, Irvington, at the Coronet, Nelson A. Rockefeller and George Goldberg, 1960; 1008.15/95 (Box 3)
  - New York, Albany, Pageant Magazine Photographs, 1960; 1008.15/1295 - 1008.15/1316 (Box 3)
  - NY, Long Island, Merrick Trip, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960; 1008.15/1291 (Box 3)
  - New York, New York City, Hotel Astor, Nelson A. Rockefeller with David Sullivan, 1960; 1008.15/124 - 1008.15/128 (Box 3)
  - Seaway Skyway, unveiling of painting, 1960; 1008.15/52 - 1008.15/54 (Box 3)
  - WA, Seattle World's Fair, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1960; 1008.15/1317 - 1008.15/1318 (Box 3)
  - Hungarian Refugee Children, circa 1960; 1008.15/1295 (Box 3)